THOMAS SHAW

SUMMARY

I am a dedicated Full Stack Software Developer with an intense focus on expanding my expertise. My customer service and communication skills have been honed by years of delivering technical solutions to clients in a simple and straightforward manner.

C# | ASP.Net | ASP.Net
Core | Razor | MVC |
JavaScript | JQuery | SQL
Server | Node.js | BootStrap
| CSS | Grid | FlexBox |
HTML | AGILE | REST API |
Git

CONTACT

■TShaw516@gmail.com

Q Cleveland, Ohio

in TShaw516

C TShaw516

EDUCATION

We Can Code IT Jan. certificate of 2020 to software Apr. development, 2020

The Ohio State Aug. 2007 to University June 2010

University of Aug. 2010 to Akron June 2013

EMPLOYMENT

Best Buy

Advanced Repair Agent

Oct. 2019 to Current

- Repaired both hardware and software problems on client devices
- Advised clients on their technology needs using simple and relatable terminology
- Experience with troubleshooting both basic and advanced issues experienced by users

Computer Sales

Akron, Ohio Aug. 2007 to Dec. 2017

• Constructed ideal technological solutions for clients. Took client requests and translated them into a solution and then reiterated technical solutions back to the client in an understandable fashion.

RT Medical Services

Medical Billing / Coding

Aug. 2014 to Current

- Experience using ICD-10 in order to bill appropriate CPT and HCPS code
- Used extensive knowledge of local coverage determinations in order to provide services with flawless compliance
- Handled compliance assurance and re-determination and appeal requests

American Income Life

Benefits Analyst

Cleveland, Ohio Dec. 2017 to Aug. 2019

- Provided supplemental benefits options to workers at a variety of companies
- Required extensive knowledge of benefits provided by individual companies and how to complement these packages

PROJECTS

BlueSky Travel Itinerary Project C# / Virtual Studio - ASP.NET Core - MVC - WebApp Current

An application used for collaborating with co-travelers on vacation planning.

University Clinic Project C# / Visual Studio

Current

C# / VISUAI Studio

An application used to manage employees in a hospital setting including assigning salary and job duties

Blog Project

Current

 $\label{eq:charge_continuous} \textit{C\#-HTML-CSS--ASP.NET/Visual Studio-MVC-WebApp}$

An application used to post blogs and sort them by category and tag.

SKILLS

CERTIFICATIONS: Apple ACiT iOS Certified, Apple OS X Certified

LANGUAGE: Proficient level of French